<?xml version="1.0"?>
<PresetGroup xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" Label="All Career Gigs EP19">
  <Preset Label="&lt;i&gt;There once was a spirit, grown from soil and love, who spent their days tending a garden. The garden belonged to a mother of nature, who watched over creatures she’d pardon. Now, the spirit’s first error was insecure terror, and their purpose felt more like a chore. So attempting great power, like their beloved flower, they let envy spread like a spore...&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;font color=&quot;#1E81E6&quot;&gt;Solve Riddles.&lt;/font&gt;\n (questGig_EP19Quests_GreenMan)" Value="436764" />
  <Preset Label="&lt;i&gt;Down by a Creek, alongside a road, sat a house like a true short stack. The man who resides, was searching for guides, to fix his marriage which was &lt;b&gt;wack&lt;/b&gt;. So during the day, he decided to stay and clean up the house—make it shine! But after an hour, he took a long shower, and stated the mess should be fine. Then deep in the night, from sparkle or might, the house was made all neat and clean. And when they awoke, that syrupy bloke took credit for scrubbing the scene...&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;font color=&quot;#1E81E6&quot;&gt;Talk to Sims and Find a Fairy Ring to Use.&lt;/font&gt;\n (questGig_EP19Quests_Gnome_Narrative)" Value="440746" />
  <Preset Label="&lt;i&gt;There once stood a Gnome, taller than a throne, who lost what was once so dear. Away to his garden, the walls he did harden, secluded alone and in fear. The children came quick, for the Gnome they had kicked had locked himself far from their feet. But due to the walls, his plants he enthralled, had withered and died from no heat. So could such a Sim, hear a simple man’s whim, to waken the beast from within? I'll send you along, you won’t need a song. Just simply show them compassion...&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;font color=&quot;#1E81E6&quot;&gt;Obtain Fairy Dust and Wake The Great Gnome.&lt;/font&gt;\n (questGig_EP19Quests_Gnome_Great)" Value="440747" />
  <Preset Label="&lt;i&gt;Upon a full moon, at a Werewolf’s high noon, emotions were stirring down under. A boy had just met a creature to pet, but a greeting with Greg he did blunder. He went screaming away, telling neighbors &lt;b&gt;that stray&lt;/b&gt; had pierced the boy’s skin with its teeth. But no marks were seen, the boy’s skin was clean, and the story was swept underneath. Again and again, that sweet charlatan would spin tale after tale about Greg. Now just wait and see, for his ultimate plea, was that Greg had consumed his whole leg...&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;font color=&quot;#1E81E6&quot;&gt;Deliver or Consume an Item.&lt;/font&gt;\n (questGig_EP19Quests_Apothecary_Fetch)" Value="441617" />
  <Preset Label="&lt;i&gt;A couple alone, sits off in the grass, deep in thought, not a care in the world. They won't need a shelter, or toilet, or bath, they sleep on the ground all unfurled. This natural lifestyle is one that they've earned, building strength to survive on the knoll. But hey, have you heard? Of the old urban legend? The one where the worms take control...&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;font color=&quot;#1E81E6&quot;&gt;Craft or Use an Elixir. Forage and Deliver Item.&lt;/font&gt;\n (questGig_EP19Quests_Apothecary_Craft)" Value="441618" />
  <Preset Label="&lt;i&gt;Two gardens sat fine, across the yard line, of two neighbors who varied in skill. One garden grew tall, with crops ready for fall, and the other was withered and ill. Now that neighbor in need, did not care to weed, and put all the blame on the other. And the cause of their doubt, to the garden’s clear drought, were pixies that came in to smother...&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;font color=&quot;#1E81E6&quot;&gt;Obtain and Deliver an Item.&lt;/font&gt;\n (questGig_EP19Quests_Fairy)" Value="441670" />
  <Preset Label="&lt;i&gt;A freezer so sunny, this cute Social Bunny, was bouncing along in the grass. She took a big hop before needing to stop and peer at a tiny young lass. This chicken was caught, in a moment of thought, watching Sims try out some composting. “I'll bet you a grand, if you can withstand, competitive social trash-posting.” The chick said “For sure!”, they knew they’d endure, for their beak was good with collision. But to prevent damage, the chicken must manage a slow ‘n steady disposition...&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;font color=&quot;#1E81E6&quot;&gt;Obtain an Item, Live Naturally, and Talk to Sims.&lt;/font&gt;\n (questGig_EP19Quests_Trade_Nature)" Value="441722" />
  <Preset Label="&lt;i&gt;There was once a man, built in physique, who relished a good love affair. He’d sprinkle his charm wherever he went, and many girls flocked to his care. But a woman in red did not fall for his tricks, and left the poor fella on read. So from this rejection, to his feigned affection, a plot he concocted was bred...&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;font color=&quot;#1E81E6&quot;&gt;Deliver a Given Item.&lt;/font&gt;\n (questGig_EP19Quests_Trade_Fetch)" Value="441723" />
  <Preset Label="&lt;i&gt;A family who owned everything in the world had not finished grabbing their share. And these Sims you should know, up in their chateau, had money to spend without care. Now, Geoffrey thought schools, but dear Nancy thought pools, should become their next big endeavor. But they both had such pride and could not decide on just whose idea was more clever...&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;font color=&quot;#1E81E6&quot;&gt;Ask Fairies for an Item to Deliver.&lt;/font&gt;\n (questGig_EP19Quests_Liaison_Fetch)" Value="441780" />
  <Preset Label="&lt;i&gt;Through mist or through rock, found deep in a cove, a land lived alone and in secret. And any reward that could be discovered, the Sim was allowed to just keep it. Now this place was made for all of life’s creatures, but nobody knew its true worth. Except Mother Nature, and her nomenclature, which stated “it’s deep in the earth”. So go my dear friend, figure out what she means, and catch your reward if you dare. You can teleport, the travel is short, then find out what’s hidden in there...&lt;/i&gt;\n\n&lt;font color=&quot;#1E81E6&quot;&gt;Travel and Collect a Fish.&lt;/font&gt;\n (questGig_EP19Quests_Liaison_Travel)" Value="441781" />
</PresetGroup>